ROSHANE MILLER

WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

https://portfolio-brezus.vercel.app/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A self-taught frontend developer of three years, seeking a position to utilize skills in web development technologies such as React, Tailwind, and Git, to collaborate with a team of developers and deliver exceptional results for clients. Building websites and honing customer service experience over the past three years has provided the ability to comprehend client's needs and effectively communicate with them.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS
- IS
- REACT IS
- NEXT JS
- REST API
- STYLED COMPONENTS
- TAILWIND,

- FIREBASE,
- SANITY IO
- GIT
- GITHUB
- PHOTOSHOP
- VSCODE
- FIGMA

- FIGMA
- Web Design

WORK HISTORY

FREELANCE FRONTEND DEVELOPER 02/2022 to 02/2022

Ralston Studios, Richmond, VA

- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Through effective communication, collaborated with client to seamlessly incorporate additional desired features.

PRODUCE CLERK 10/2020 to 02/2022

Bjs, Stratford, CT

- Pleasantly greeted customers and provided prompt and courteous service.
- Received and unloaded new items upon delivery and checked products for damage and order accuracy.
- Assisted customers with price checking fruits and vegetables and finding requested items in department.
- Checked for outdated and overripe grocery items and removed from inventory.

CASHIER 10/2015 to 02/2018 **Kroger**, Richmond, VA

- Operated cash register for cash, check and credit card transactions with excellent accuracy levels.
- Worked flexible schedule and extra shifts to meet business needs.
- Helped customers complete purchases, locate items and join reward programs.
- Restocked and organized merchandise in front lanes.

EDUCATION

St. Georges College, Kingston, JA **High School Diploma**, 09/2014

CERTIFICATIONS

The Frontend Developer Career Path Dec 2021 - Jun 2022